[
     {
         "question": "Search everywhere",
         "answer": "double shift"
      },
      {
          "question": "Go to class",
          "answer": "cmd O"
      },
      {
          "question": "Go to Line",
          "answer": "cmd L"
      },
      {
          "question": "Go to declaration",
          "answer": "cmd B"
      },
      {
          "question": "Find Usage",
          "answer": "option F7"
      },
      {
          "question": "Basic code completion(the name of any class, method or variable)",
          "answer": "ctrl space"
      },
      {
          "question": "Smart code completion(filters the list of methods and variables by expected type)",
          "answer": "ctrl shift space"
      },
      {
          "question": "Complete statement",
          "answer": "cmd shift return"
      },
      {
          "question": "Parameter info(within method call arguments)",
          "answer": "cmd P"
      },
      {
          "question": "Quick documentation lookup",
          "answer": "shift F1"
      },
      {
          "question": "Generate code...(Getters, Seters, Constructors, hashCode/equals, toString)",
          "answer": "cmd N, ctrl return, ctrl N"
      },
      {
          "question": "Override methods",
          "answer": "ctrl O"
      },
      {
          "question": "Implement methods",
          "answer": "ctrl I"
      },
      {
          "question": "Surround with...(if..else, try..catch, for, synchronized, etc)",
          "answer": "cmd option T"
      },
      {
          "question": "Comment/uncomment with line comment",
          "answer": "cmd /"
      },
      {
          "question": "Comment/uncomment with block comment",
          "answer": "cmd option /"
      },
      {
          "question": "Select successibely increasing code blocks",
          "answer": "option upArrow"
      },
      {
          "question": "Decrease current selection to previous state",
          "answer": "option downArrow"
      },
      {
          "question": "Context info",
          "answer": "ctrl shift Q"
      },
      {
          "question": "Showintention actions and quick-fixes",
          "answer": "option return"
      },
      {
          "question": "Refomat code",
          "answer": "cmd option L"
      },
      {
          "question": "Optimize imports",
          "answer": "ctrl option O"
      },
      {
          "question": "Auto-indent line(s)",
          "answer": "ctrl option I"
      },
      {
          "question": "Indent selected lines",
          "answer": "tab"
      },
      {
          "question": "Cut current line or selected block to clipboard",
          "answer": "cmd X"
      },
      {
          "question": "Copy current line or selected block to clipboard",
          "answer": "cmd C"
      },
      {
          "question": "paste from clipboard",
          "answer": "cmd V"
      },
      {
          "question": "Paste from recent buffers",
          "answer": "cmd shift V"
      },
      {
          "question": "Duplicate current line or selected block",
          "answer": "cmd D"
      },
      {
          "question": "Delete line at caret",
          "answer": "cmd backspace"
      },
      {
          "question": "Smart line join",
          "answer": "ctrl shift J"
      },
      {
          "question": "Smart line split",
          "answer": "cmd return"
      },
      {
          "question": "Start new line",
          "answer": "shift return"
      },
      {
          "question": "Toggle case for word at caret or selected block",
          "answer": "cmd shift U"
      },
      {
          "question": "Select till code block end/start",
          "answer": "cmd shift ] / cmd shift ["
      },
      {
          "question": "Delete to word end",
          "answer": "option delete"
      },
      {
          "question": "Delete to word start",
          "answer": "option backspace"
      },
      {
          "question": "Expand/collapse code block",
          "answer": "cmd + / cmd -"
      },
      {
          "question": "Expend all",
          "answer": "cmd shift +"
      },
      {
          "question": "Collapse all",
          "answer": "cmd shift -"
      },
      {
          "question": "Close active editor tab",
          "answer": "cmd W"
      }
]